Stocks and bonds are moving higher....
股票，债券今天全都上涨了…
Why are we watching the Business Channel?
我们为什么看商业台？
Because the other day I saw there was a stock with my initials,MEG,on it.
因为我前几天看到有支股票 是我的名字的缩写MEG
Sometimes it takes two or three hours before it comes up again.
有时我得苦等两，三个小时 才又会再看到
But when it does,it's exciting.
但是看到的时候蛮兴奋的
Okay,honey,you really need a job.
蜜糖，我看你是真的需要工作
Dad says he knows someone you can call for an interview.
摩妮卡，说到这个，爸说 他认识一个人你可以去应徵
Right there! That's the third sign today. Right there.
那是今天的第三个预兆了 看！
On behalf of everyone, I'd just like to say,"Huh?"
我在替在座的每一位 说一声“什么？”
No,you just said "dad." And everywhere I go today...
因为你刚刚说了“爸” 今天我不管到什么地方去…
... I keep getting signs telling me to go see my father.
…我都一直得到 叫我去看我爸的预兆
Like when I was walking over here and I passed a buffet.
像我来这里的时候 我经过一个酒“吧”
Which is my father's last name.
你们知道吗？我爸爸就姓巴
And they were serving franks...
我爸爸的名字是法兰…
...which is his first name minus the "s" at the end.
…而他们也有法兰克福香肠
And there was a rotisserie with a spinning chicken.
还有一家店呢 烤架上有鸡在转的烤鸡店
His lndian name?
他的印第安名？
No. Because I chickened out the last time...
不是，因为我上次去见他时…
...when I tried to meet him. So coincidences? I don't think so.
…临“机”脱逃了 我不认为哦
-Very freaky. -Eerie.
奇哉怪哉 怪透了
Who wants the last hamburger?
最后一个汉堡谁要？
That's it. Now I have to go see him.
好了，够了，我非去不可了
Why?
为什么？
Hamburger? McDonald's?
汉堡？麦当劳？
Old McDonald had a farm. My dad is a pharmacist.
麦老先生有块地 我爸是“低”头配药的
The One With the Bullies
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第21集 两个小流氓
Man,I am so beat.
老兄，我累歪了
You wanna forget racquetball and hang out?
我们最好别去打什么球了 留在这里混吧
Yeah,all right.
对，好吧
-Hey,you're in our seats. -Sorry,we didn't know.
那是我们的位置 抱歉，我们不知道
We were sitting there.
我们本来坐那里的
Okay. There is one more way to say it.
这还有另外一种说法
Who knows it?
谁知道？
-Was that supposed to be funny? -Actually,I was going for colorful.
你这是在说笑话吗？ 不，我在说多姿多采的话
-What's with this guy? -What's with you?
这砘镌趺戳耍 你怎么了？
Nothing. Nothing's with him.
没什么，他没怎么
Enjoy your coffee.
请慢用咖啡
What just happened?
发生了什么事了？
I just took your hat. See,I can be funny too.
我刚拿了你的帽子 你看，我也能妙趣横生
My joke is that I took your hat.
我的笑话就是拿了你的帽子
That is funny.
那真有趣啊
Can I have it back?
还给我，好吗？
You know what? I think you're very funny.
你知道吗？我觉得你很风趣
Kudos on that hat joke.
我真的好崇拜你哦
But come on,guys, just give him back the hat.
别这样，两位 把帽子还给他嘛
Why should we?
为什么？
Because it's a special hat.
因为那是顶特别的帽子
He bought it because he was feeling down one day.
有一天他的心情很不好
So he got the hat...
所以他就买了那顶帽子…
...to cheer himself up,you know?
…来帮自己打气
-Chandler -Stop talking. Stop talking now.
钱德… 别说了，别再说了
Let me get this straight. You're stealing my hat?
让我先搞清楚 你抢了我的帽子？
You got a problem?
你看不过去吗？
I just want to make sure we're on the same page.
不，我只是想确定 我们大家互相了解
How'd the interview go?
面试结果怎么样？
It bit.
逊毙了
It was a 50s theme restaurant.
那是一家50年代主题的餐厅
I'd have to cook in a costume and dance on the counter.
我得穿戏服做菜在柜台上跳舞
I was a sous chef at Cafe des Artistes.
我以前是艺术家餐厅的主厨
How can I take a job where I have to make Laverne-and-Curly Fries?
我是说，我怎能接受一个 我得做QQ脆薯的工作呢
-Don't do it. -How can I not do it?
那就别做啊 我怎么能不做呢？
I have $127 in the bank!
我银行里面只剩下127块了
Monica,relax. Go get a beer.
摩妮卡，放轻松，去拿瓶啤酒
I don't want a beer.
我不想喝啤酒
Who said it was for you?
谁说是给你的？
What's the matter?
你们两个怎么了？
Some mean guys at the coffeehouse took my hat.
咖啡厅里 有个恶汉抢了我的帽子
-No! -You're kidding?
不会吧 你开玩笑？
It was ridiculous. These guys were bullies.
简直荒唐透了 这些人是霸王
Actual bullies.
是真正的霸王
We're grownups. This kind of stuff isn't supposed to happen anymore.
你看，我们是大人了 我们不该会再碰上这种事了
Oh,no,wait a minute. I have no one.
不，等一下，我孤家寡人
Let's go down there and get your hat back.
我们应该过去把帽子给拿回来
Forget it. It's probably stripped and sold for parts by now.
算了吧，说不定 已经被拆成零件给卖掉了
-I went up! -What?
我涨了 什么？
My stock,MEG,it went up two points.
我的股票MEG，涨了两点
Do you realize that if I'd invested my $127 in myself yesterday...
若我昨天把我的127元 投资在我自己身上…
...that l'd,like,have a lot more than that today.
…那我就会比我今天有钱了
You know what? I'm going to do it.
知道吗？我要放手一搏
-Do what? -Put all my money in me.
搏什么？ 拿钱投资我
You don't know a thing about the stock market.
摩妮卡，你在鬼扯什么？ 你对股市一窍不通
What's to know? Buy,sell. High,low. Bears,bulls.
要通什么？ 买，卖，高，低，空头，多头
Yes,Manhattan.
喂，曼哈顿
Telephone number for the stock...
麻烦帮我查一下股票…
...selling store.
…商店
See? I told you these pillows would be a good idea.
你看 我说应该带枕头来是对的吧
Oh,God.
天啊
Here we go.
就这样了
For the first time in my life, I'm gonna say,"Hi,Birth Father!"
我就要说出我这辈子的 第一声“嗨，生父”了
-We love you. We're here for you. -Good luck.
我们爱你，我们支持你 一切顺利
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey,Rach,you want some sandwich?
瑞秋，要不要三明治？
What is in that?
里面有什么？
Olive loaf and ham spread. No mayo.
橄榄酱，火腿酱，没美乃滋
No,because mayo, that would make it gross.
不…再加美乃滋就恶心了
-Run,Phoebe,run! -No,no,doggy,please!
跑，菲比，跑… 不要，狗狗，拜托
I do so want to love all animals. Please,no. Back off!
我爱所有的动物 给它骨头，拿骨头来
-You got a bone? -Are you kidding?
有没有骨头？ 开什么玩笑？
Look,kibbles! Bits!
看…
Get the hell off my leg, you yippity piece of crap!
放开我 你这只烂东西
Okay. All right. We have a problem.
好了，我们碰上难题了
Why don't you take his trampoline?
你为什么不拿他的弹簧垫？
Okay,here,I know what we can do.
我知道怎么办了
Okay,doggy,get the sandwich!
狗狗，去检三明治
Go get the sandwich! Good doggy. Get the sandwich!
去检三明治啊，快点
The dog will lick himself but he will not touch your sandwich.
乔伊，它宁可舔自己 也不碰你的三明治
What does that tell you?
那告诉你什么？
-lf he's not going to eat it,I will. -Are you crazy?
它不吃的话，我自己吃 你疯了你？
He's just a little dog.
它是小狗而已
-Hey. -What?
嘿 干嘛？
Do you have to be a Century 21 real-estate agent...
你一定要当房地产经纪人…
...to get to wear those cool jackets?
…才能穿着那么酷的外套吗？
Do you say this stuff to girls?
你会跟女生这样搭讪吗？
Isn't that the guy who used to wear your hat?
那不是你帽子的旧主人吗？
And look where they're sitting.
看他们坐在哪里了
You're joking,right? You guys just walked through the door.
你在说笑吧？你们才刚进门
Maybe we didn't make it clear enough.
或许我们说得不够清楚
This couch belongs to us.
这个沙发是我们的
I'll tell you what, you call the couch...
这样吧，你们叫一声沙发…
...and then we'll call the couch...
…然后我们也对着它叫一声…
...and we'll see who it comes to.
…看它会到谁那里去
You know,I keep wondering why you two are still sitting here.
我一直不懂 你们为什么还赖在这个地方？
All right,that's it.
好了，够了
I have had enough of this.
我受够这些狗屁了，好吗？
Gunther.
阿刚
These guys are trying to take our seat.
这两个砘 想抢我们的座位
Fellas,these guys were here first.
两位，他们先来的
Oh,sorry,didn't realize.
抱歉，我们不知道
There you go.
好了
Thank you,Gunther.
谢谢，阿刚
We didn't want to have to go and do that.
是你们逼我们这么做的
He told on us?
他打小报告？
You told on us?
你打小报告？
Well,pal,you didn't give me much of a choice.
兄弟，你们逼得我别无选择
-Don't play with his thing. -I know.
别玩他的东西 我知道
All right.
很好，我们到外面解决
Let's take this outside.
我们到外面解决
"Let's take this outside?"
“我们到外面解决”
Who talks like that?
谁会这么说？
The guy who's about to kick your ass talks like that.
即将要痛扁你们的人会这么说
You had to ask.
谁叫你多嘴呢
Okay,okay,look. See...
好吧…
...the thing is,we're not gonna fight you guys.
…我们不想用武力来解决
Here's the deal.
那么这样好了
You won't have to,so long as you never ever show your faces here again.
你们保证从今以后 不踏入这家咖啡厅
I think you played the Gunther card too soon.
你太早把阿刚抬出来了吧
Hey,Pheebs,I think you're good to go.
菲菲，我想你可以上去了
Yeah,I don't know.
我不知道
What's the matter?
又怎么了？
I just think that this was a really bad sign.
我是觉得这是个很不好的预兆
Like the beast at the threshold.
我是说像门槛上的野兽啦
It's just I have no family left, except for my grandmother.
我已经没有别的亲人了 除了我奶奶之外
But let's face it,she's not gonna be around forever.
可是面对现实吧 她又不会永远都活着
Despite what she says.
不管怎么说
And I have a sister who I've barely spoken to since we shared a womb.
我有个除了在子宫里面 几乎没有说过话的姐姐
I don't know. This is my real father...
这是我真正的父亲…
...and I want things to be, like,just right.
…我只是要一切完美嘛
I completely understand.
我完全了解
Whatever you need.
对，随你要怎么样
Hey,you want to go home?
你要回家吗？
Okay,thanks. Sorry,again.
谢了，对不起
What was that?
那是什么？
I'm guessing the threshold's clear now.
我猜现在门槛没有狗了
I want to buy five shares of SGJ. Now.
我要买五股XTJ 我现在就要
Come on,time is money,my friend!
快点，时间就是金钱
Thank you!
谢谢
"Time is money,my friend?"
“时间就是金钱”？
You missed "Takes money to make money"...
“时间就是金钱”…
...and "Don't make me come down there and kick your Wall Street butt."
…还有，“别逼我 过去踢你的华尔街屁股”
I made $ 17 before breakfast. What have you done?
我早餐前就赚了十七块耶 那你做了什么？
I had breakfast here, so technically I saved $3.50.
我早餐在这个地方吃的 所以技术上我省了三块半
How did you make $17?
你怎么赚十七块的？
Well,my financially challenged friends...
我的经济白痴朋友…
...I split my money and I bought some shares of CHP and ZXY.
…我用我的钱分别买了些 CHP跟ZXY股
How come those?
你怎么选的？
Well,CHP because I used to have a crush on Erik Estrada.
CHP是因为我暗恋过 “加州公路巡警”的奇普
And ZXY because I think it sounds "zexy."
ZXY 那是听起来很“劲”感啊
What happened to MEG?
那你的…MEG呢？
MEG was good for me,but I dumped her.
MEG帮我赚过钱 但是被我甩了
My motto is,"Get out before they go down."
我的座右铭 是在“疲软”以前出场的
That is so not my motto.
这倒不是我的作风
How's the dog?
狗好点了没？
Okay. I talked to the vet. People are so nice upstate.
我跟兽医谈好了 纽约州的人真好
He said the little fella's gonna be okay,and I can get him tomorrow.
他说那个小砘锊换嵊形侍 明天我可以去接它了
-Good. -Thank God.
好，好极了 谢天谢地
But he did have to have a bunch of stitches.
可是他必须帮它缝好多针
And he said that only once in a blue moon does a dog's ear grow back.
而且他还说除非天下红雨 狗才会再长出耳朵来的
So still hoping.
所以还有一点点希望
Now are you going to call your dad to let him know that his dog is okay?
那你现在要打电话告诉你爸 他的狗没事了吗？
I don't want to meet my father over the phone.
我不想在电话上跟我爸相认
What will I say, "Hi,I'm the daughter you abandoned.
我该跟他先什么呢？ “我是菲比被你抛弃的女儿”
Oh,by the way,I broke your dog."
“对了，我撞伤了你的狗”
Hey,Pheebs,if you want,I'll do it.
菲菲，我可以帮你打的
Listen,just don't say anything about me,okay?
听着，拜托千万不要提我的事
Don't...
别…
... be too long with the phone.
…讲电话太久
She'll be a much better friend once the market closes.
股市收盘以后 她会是个比较好的朋友
It's a woman.
是个女的
So talk to her.
你跟她讲啊
Hello,Mrs. Buffay.
巴太太
I know where your dog is.
我知道你的狗在哪里
I want you to know he'll be returned to you almost as good as new...
我要你知道 我们会在24小时之内…
...within 24 hours.
…将它几乎完好如初的还给你
Goodbye.
再见
-Why the voice? -Hard to say.
干嘛装声音？ 很难讲
Your cappuccino,sir.
你的卡布基诺来了
Thank you.
谢谢
-This is better than the coffeehouse. -Absolutely.
在这里喝比在咖啡厅好多了 对极了
How come it's not mixing with the water?
咖啡粉为什么不化？
The package says to keep it moving.
包装上说你必须要不断的搅拌
Stir and drink,never let it settle.
搅拌，喝 别让咖啡停下来
This is ridiculous.
这太荒唐了吧
After I get back from my niece's christening...
这样吧，等我从 外甥女的洗礼回来之后呢…
...I'll go to the coffeehouse with you and we'll have a cup of coffee.
…我陪你们两个到中央公园去 我们好好的享受一杯咖啡
No problem. Joey's there.
没问题的，有乔伊在
I don't want to have to have Joey with me every time I want decent coffee.
不，我不希望每一次 我想喝一杯好咖啡
And I don't want to drink cappuccino with a "k."
我也不想一辈子 喝这个牌子的泡沫咖啡
I say you and I go and stand up to those guys.
我认为我们应该回咖啡厅去 勇敢的面对那些人
All right,hang on a second there,Custer.
好吧，你先等一等，将军
Ross,have you ever been beaten up before?
真的，罗斯 你以前有没有被扁过？
Yeah,sure.
有啊，当然有
By someone besides Monica?
被摩妮卡以外的人？ 没有
So what?
所以呢？
So we get beaten up. Maybe that's something a man has to go through.
就算被扁又怎么样？也许每个 男人都得经历过一次这个…
Like a rite of passage or something.
成人式之类什么的
Couldn't we just lose our virginities again?
不能再失去一次童贞就好吗？
Because I think actually mine's growing back.
因为我想我的又长回来了
-I need $100. -What?
我需要借100 什么？
Welcome home.
欢迎光临
-I need $100. -For what?
我需要借一百块 干嘛？
-To get back in the game. -When did you get out?
我得回到场上玩 你什么时候退场的？
I lost it all. I lost it.
不知道，我赔光了
I've come to terms with it, you have to,too.
我接受事实了，你也得这样
Look,Mon,I'm really sorry.
听着，摩妮卡，我很遗撼
Where are we on the $100?
你到底借不借？
I don't have it.
我没钱啊
But I need it!
可是我需要
Otherwise,I'll have to take that diner job.
那我得去那个烂馆子工作了
You know,with the dancing and the costumes.
你知道的 就是跳舞还有穿戏服
I don't want to have to wear flame-retardant boobs.
我不想穿 连火都烧不着的假胸部
Nobody does,honey.
没人想，蜜糖
Noodle!
面面
Oh,my God. What the hell happened to my dog?
老天啊，我的狗到底怎么了？
It was an accident.
那是个意外
And the woman who did this would never hurt a dog on purpose.
而且那个肇事的女人 绝不会蓄意伤害一只狗的
She's a vegetarian.
她吃素
Are these stitches?
这是什么？缝线？
Yeah,eight of them. That's 56 to him.
对，八针 对狗来说是56针啦
If it's raining,you can't let him look up...
还有，下雨的时候…
... because that cone will fill up fast.
…不要让它抬头太久 因为那玩意儿装不了多少水的
Thanks for bringing back what's left of him.
谢谢你送它的残骸回来
-ls Frank home? -How do you know Frank?
没问题，法兰在吗？ 你怎么认识他的？
Just from a long time ago. Is he here?
那是很久以前的事，他在吗？
What?
什么事啊？
I mean Frank Senior.
我是说，老的法兰
He went out for groceries.
他去买日用品了
Will he be back soon?
他很快回来吗？
He left four years ago. We're expecting him back any minute.
他四年前去的 所以我们猜他随时会回来
I'm gonna go.
那我要走了
I'm sorry about the dog. Everything.
对不起，关于… 关于那只狗
I'm sorry.
对不起
Hey,lady!
小姐
Hey,wait up!
等一下
-How do you know my dad? -Well,I don't really.
你怎么认识我老爸的？ 我不认识他
Just genetically.
基因上认得
He's kind of my dad too.
他也算是我老爸吧
Heavy.
不得了
So did he ever talk about me... Phoebe?
他有没有提过我…菲比？
No,but he didn't really talk about anything.
没有，不过他一向沉默是金啦
Except stilts.
除了高~
-Stilts? -Yeah,he loved stilts.
高~？ 对啊，他爱高~
One time,I was upstairs stealing cigarettes out of my mom's purse...
有一次我在楼上，正在偷 我妈皮包里面的香烟时…
...and all of a sudden I look over...
…突然间我张望了一下…
...and there's Dad's head, bobbing past the window.
…看到我爸的头从窗外经过
He just had this big smile on his face and he was waving...
他脸上满是笑意地 向我挥了一挥手…
...because he was happiest when he was on his stilts.
…因为他踩高~的时候 就是他最高兴的时候了
I don't know what to do with that.
我根本不会踩那玩意儿
Me neither.
我也是
So are you,like,my big sister?
所以你是我姐姐？
This is huge. You can buy me beer!
真不得了，你可以请我喝啤酒
I'm not gonna.
我不要
But you know what's cool? If you had a friend named Pete,I could say...
知道怎么样最酷吗？ 如果你有个朋友叫做彼得…
... "I know Pete. He's friends with my brother."
…那我就可说“彼得，我认得 他是我弟弟的朋友”
-I got a friend named Mark. -That'll work too.
我有个朋友叫马克 那也可以啊
Cool. All right.
酷，好
So maybe,you know, I could give you a call sometime.
或许改天我可以打个电话给你
We could talk or something.
我们可以好好聊聊或什么的
-Yeah,that'd be okay. -All right.
好啊，那会很好 好
I'm in the book.
电话簿上有我的电话
So stilts,huh?
那…高~？
If you want,I can show you where he hit his head on the rain gutter.
你要的话，我可以带你去看 他头撞到排水管的那个地方
We did it. We're here. We are standing our ground.
我们办到了，我们在这儿 我们坚守我们的立场
-How long does coffee take? -Would you come on? Come on!
一杯咖啡到底要煮多久？ 快点？快点呀
Thank you.
谢谢
-There we go. -I think we proved our point.
好了，喝完了 我想我们证明了
-You burn your mouth? -Cannot feel my tongue.
烫到嘴了没有？ 舌头没感觉了
Bullies! Big bullies!
霸王，大霸王
Look who's here. It's the weenies.
看看谁来了？是胆小鬼们
Did we not make ourselves clear the other day?
我们那天讲得不够清楚 是不是？
That's why we're here.
所以我们才来
Yes,we're standing our ground.
对，我们在坚守立场
Apparently.
你也看的出来吧
Let's do this already.
少说废话了
You got a weapon?
你那是什么？武器？
A nice watch. I don't want to break it on your ribs.
一只好表 我不想在槌你的时候弄坏它
All right,let's do this.
来吧，来呀
Question: If I don't care about my watch,can I use it as a weapon?
我有问题，若我不在乎我的表 我可以拿下来当武器吗？
-What do you mean? -It's sharp,it's metal.
什么意思？ 这很利，是金属做的
I think I can do some serious damage with it.
我想这可以用来 发挥很大的杀伤力
No,you can't use your watch.
不，你不能用手表
Or your keys.
或钥匙
Here's what we'll do.
听我说，这样好了
We'll put all keys and watches in the hat over there.
把所有的钥匙和手表 都放在这个帽子里面摆在那里
All right?
好吗？
All right,come on,man. Let's do it!
好了，来吧…
Before I forget,are we hitting faces?
趁我还记得，脸可以打吗？
Of course. Why wouldn't you hit faces?
当然可以打，脸为何不能打？
I have to work on Monday. I have a big presentation.
因为我星期一还得上班 我得上台说话
Actually,I gotta show this apartment tomorrow...
我明天要带人去看房子…
...and this no-faces thing might not be a bad idea.
…所以不打脸这码子事 倒是满好的主意
Nothing from the neck up.
脖子以上不准打
Or the waist down.
或腰部以下
-Dana's ovulating. -Really? You guys trying again?
黛娜在排卵期 真的？你们又在试了？
Let me get this straight. We're talking about the middle?
好吧，让我先搞清楚 我们只能够打中间的部份吗？
Come on!
来呀
You want a piece of this? I'm standing here!
你们要打这边？还是打这边？
Those guys are taking our stuff!
你们看，我们东西被偷了
God,that was amazing. That was incredible.
天啊，那真是不可思
-You guys kicked butt! -Us? What about you guys?
你们好厉害 我们？那你们呢？
You really gave it to old Mr. Clean back there.
你们真的 给了那个老贼颜色瞧了
-He was a big guy. -Yeah,he was,wasn't he?
那砘锍さ煤米嘲 没错，不是吗？
I wouldn't know, having missed everything.
是呀，我不知道，我全错过了
Don't do that to yourself.
不要太苛责自己了
Any one of us could have tripped over that little girl's jump rope.
我们不管谁都可以 被那个小女孩的跳绳给绊倒
So listen,guys...
对了，两位，那我们…
...are we okay here?
…没事了吧？
We're okay.
没事了
So can I have my hat back?
那帽子可以还给我了吗？
Oh,my God. Look at her.
看看她
Hi,Monica!
摩妮卡
How's it going?
顺利吗？
Hey,nice boobs.
好美的波
Guys,guys. Check this out.
各位…看看这个
Excellent.
太棒了